Guide to the Simon Bauer papers,1932-2002.
Bauer, Simon papers, 1932-2002
  - #267. Vibrational Relaxation Time Measurements via CRIIF, A. D. Devir and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 69, 2682 (1978). (Box 3)
  - NSF Award, Zia Imani (Box 3)
  - #268. The Early Stages of Pyrolysis and oxidation of Methane, K. Tabayashi and S. H. Bauer, Combustion & Flame 34, 63 (1979). (Box 3)
  - #269. Summary of Four Center Problem, S. H. Bauer, Ann. Re. Phys. Chem. 30, 271 (1979). (Box 3)
  - #270. molecular vs System Relaxation Times, S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Ed. 56, 382 (1979). Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors~vThe Condensation of Si, K. Tabayashi and S. H. Bauer Proceedings of the 12th International Symposium on Shock Tubes and Waves, Magnes Press, Jerusalem, 1980, p.409. (Box 3)
  - #271. Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors. VI. The Condensation of Silicon, K. Tabayashi and S. H. Bauer, (1980) (Box 3)
  - #272. Cluster Size Distribution from Homogeneous Condensation: A Stochastic Model, C. F. Wilcox, Jr., S. Russo, and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 83, 897 (1979). (Box 3)
  - #273. Bistable Regime for a CO, Laser, with SF, Intracavity as a Saturable Absorber, S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 66, 100 (1979). (Box 4)
  - #274. Bistable Regime for a CO, Laser (II), S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, Appl. Phys. 24, 45 (1981). 20 (Box 4)
  - #275. Gas Phase Kinetics of the Syn Anti Isomerizations of H3CONO via NMR, S. H. Bauer and N. S. True, J. Phys. Chem. 84, 2507 (1980) (Box 4)
  - #276. A Temperature-drift Technique for Locating moderately Excited States, S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 84, 3055 (1980). (Box 4)
  - #277. Rotational Isomers of Methyl Formate, Located by the TD Technique, S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 84, 3061 (1980). (Box 4)
  - #278. Shock Tubes: S. H. Bauer in the McGrawHill Encyclopedia of Science and Technology, (5th Ed), April 1982, p. 377ff. Updated August 1989 for 7th Edition. (Box 4)
  - #279. Stimulated Emissions from Atomic Iron, Generated by Excitation of Iron Carbonyl, J. Krasinski, S. H. Bauer and K. L. Kompa, optics Commun. 35, 363 (1980). (Box 4)
  - #280. Fluorescence from Noble Gases and Various Substrates, Induced by ns Pulses of 600 keV Electrons, S. H. Bauer and J. Krasinski Report to Projektgruppe fur Laserforschung, Max Planck Gesellschaft (Munchen), May, 1980 (33pp + 2 Tables + 24 figures). (Box 4)
  - #281. (a) The Partial Reduction of Trimethoxyborane. Studies of an old Rection in a New Reactor, P. M. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 21, 1698 (1981). (Box 4)
  - #281. (b) Note on the Disproportionation of Dimethoxyborane, P.M. Jeffers and S.H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 21, 2516 (1982). © H. Fusstedter Experiments on L.P.H.P. BC1,, etc. (Box 4)
  - #281. (c) Herman Fusstetter-Experiments on L.P.H.P-BCl3, etc. (Box 4)
  - #282. (a) Homogeneous Nucleation in Supersaturated Fe and Si Vapors, and Subsequent Condensation, I, J. R. Stephens and S. H. Bauer, Proceedings of 13th Int. Symp. on Shock Tubes & Waves, (July 1981), Ed. C. Treanor and G. Hall, p. 691699. (b) Homogeneous Nucleation in Supersaturated Fe and Si Vapors, and Subsequent Condensation, II, J. R. Stephens and S. H. Bauer, Meteoritics 16, 388 (1981). © Proc. Electrochem. Soc. 837, 212 (1983). (Box 4)
  - #283. The Chemiluminescent Reaction Between H,BN(CH,), and 0('P) Atoms, P. M. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 80, 29 (1981). (Box 4)
  - #284. Chapter 11.8 in: Fifty Years of Electron Diffraction (Ed. P. Goodman), The CalTechCornell Connection (p.92), 1981. (Box 4)
  - #285. Co/Mo/Al,O, Catalyst Structure Determination by EXAFS (I). Mo Kedge in the oxidized State, NS. Chiu, S. H. Bauer, and M. F. L. Johnson, J. of Catalysis, 89, 226 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #286. Rates of Intramolecular Conversions Over Low Barriers, The Acetyl Acetones, A. Rosenberg and S. H. Bauer, presented at the 11th NERM Meeting, October, 1981, Abs. No.360. (Box 4)
  - #287. Synthesis in a Low Power Microwave Discharge Amorphous Silicon Nitride and Polycrystalline Silicon, P. M. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, J. Noncryst. Solids, 57, 189 (1983). (Box 4)
  - #288. Intramolecular Unsymmetrical OHO Bonds Thermochemistry, K. I. Lazaar and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 87, 2411.(1983). (Box 4)
  - #289. Intramolecular Conversion Rates Over Low Barriers, II. The Alkyl Nitrites, K. I. Lazaar and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 88, 3052 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #290. Second Order Rate Constants for Intramolecular Conversions Application to GasPhase NMR Relaxation Times, S. H. Bauer and K. I. Lazaar, J. Chem. Phys. 79, 2808 (1983). (Box 4)
  - #291. Spectral Analysis of the Chemiluminescence Generated by H,BX + 0(3P), P. M. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 88, 5039 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #292. Intramolecular Conversions IV. The Dimer/Monomer Dissociation in Formic Acid, K. I. Lazaar and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 107, 3769 (1985). (Box 4)
  - #293. Shock Tube Pyrolysis of Aromatic Hydrocarbons: Detection of Soot Precursors, S. H. Bauer and LM. Zhang, Presented at 14th International Symposium on Shock Tubes and Waves, August 1983 (Sydney, Australia). In the Proceedings, p.654. (Box 4)
  - #294. Overview Laser Applications to Industrial Chemistry, S. H. Bauer, SPIE Proceedings, 458, 1 (1984). An abbreviated and updated version of "On the Rational Use of Lasers for Chemical Processing," presented at 1980 Cornell Symposium on Laser Applications. (Box 4)
  - #294a. Laser Induced Photochemistry, SRI (1979), Laser Photochemistry and Diagnostics, NSF (1979), Applications of Lasers to Industrial Chemistry, SPIE (1984) (Box 4)
  - #295. Oscillating Convective Effects in SF,Ar Laser Heated Mixtures, S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 88, 5042 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #296. Intermolecular Conversions Over Low Barriers, III: Gas Phase NMR Studies of an HBonded Association, S. H. Bauer and Tomako Yamazaki, K. I. Lazaar and NS. Chiu, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 107, 743 (1985). (Box 4)
  - #297. Note on the Structure of Ba,CaMoO,, NS. Chiu and S. H. Bauer, Acta Cryst. C40, 1646 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #298. Structure Determination of Amorphous Materials via EXAFS, NS. Chiu, S. H. Bauer and M. F. L. Johnson, J. Mol. Struct. 125, 33 (1984). (Box 4)
  - #299. A Random Walk Among Accessible States, S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Ed. 63, 377 (1986). (Box 4)
  - #300. Intramolecular Conversions V. Rational Rate Constants for Reversible Unimolecular Reactions, S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 17, 367 (1985). (Box 4)
  - #301. Co/mo/Al,O, Catalyst Structure Determination by EXAFS (II). Mo K-edge in the Sulfided State, N. S. Chiu, S. H. Bauer, and M. F. L. Johnson, J. Catal. 98, 32 (1986). (Box 4)
  - #302. Stochastic Simulation of Condensation in Supersonic Expansions (Ar), C. F. Wilcox, Jr. and S. H. Bauer presented at 15th Symposium on Shock Waves and Tubes (June, 1985), and at Colloid Symposium (June, 1985); Proceedings of Symposium, Ed. D. Bershader and R. Hanson, Stanford U Press (1986), p. 783. (Box 4)
  - #303. Co/Mo/Alumina Catalyst Structure Determination by EXAFS, III. The Catalysts: Their Preparation, Characterization and HDS Activities, M. F. L. Johnson, A. P. Voss, S. H. Bauer and NS. Chiu, J. Catal. 98, 51 (1986). (Box 4)
  - #304. A Minimal Mechanism of Soot Production, S. H. Bauer and P. M. Jeffers, published by Division of Fuel Chemistry, for September 1987 ACS Meeting [Vol. 32, #3]. Revision and amplified version in Energy & Fuels, 2, 446 (1988). (Box 4)
  - #305. Intramolecular Conversions Over Low Barriers VI. The TransCis Isomerization of Monothioformic Acid, K. I. Lazaar and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 83, 85 (1985). (Box 4)
  - #306. A Multichannel, Rapid Recording Spectrometer, C. R. Dunnam, NS. Chiu and S. H. Bauer, Rev. Sci. Inst. 57, 384 (1986). (Box 4)
  - #307. A High Repetition Rate, Low Temperture Shock Tube, E. L. Resler, Jr. and S. H. Bauer, presented at 15th International Symposium on Shock Waves, Berkeley, August, 1985. Proceedings of Symposium, Ed. D. Bershader and R. Hanson, Stanford U Press (1986), p. 657. (Box 4)
  - #308. Co/Mo/Alumina Catalyst Structure Determination by EXAFS, IV. Models Derived from Studies of the Co Kedge, NS. Chiu, S. H. Bauer and M. F. L. Johnson, J. Catalysis 113, 281 (1988). (Box 4)
  - #309. Hydrogen Atom Abstraction by 0(3p) from B,H, and C,H,, JG. Choi, K. Suzuki, D. B. Borchardt and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys., 88, 6282 (1988). (Box 4)
  - #310. On the Structure of HDS Catalysts, S. H. Bauer, NS. Chiu and M. F. L. Johnson, J. Phys. Chem. 90, 4888 (1986) in P. H. Emmett Memorial Issue. (Box 4)
  - #311. The Gas Phase Kinetics of Boron and Borane A Review, S. H. Bauer, Chapter 19 in Molecular Structure and Energetics, Vol. 5 (1987), Edited by J. F. Liebman and R. Williams. (Box 4)
  - #312. Kinetics of Condensation in Supersonic Expansion, S. H. Bauer, NS. Chiu and C. F. Wilcox, Jr., J. Chem. Phys. 85, 2029 (1986) and (Gas Flow & Chem Lasers) Ed. S. Rosenwaks SpringerVerlag, Berlin (1987), p. 22. (Box 4)
  - #313. Intramolecular Conversion Over Low Barriers VII. The Aziridine Inversion Intrinsically nonRRKM, D. B. Borchardt and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 85, 4980 (1986). (Box 4)
  - #314. Vibrational Relaxation Rates of CO, (00°1) with various Collision Partners, for T < 300°K, S. H. Bauer, J. F. Caballero, R. Curtis and J. R. Wiesenfeld, J. Phys. Chem. 91, 1778 (1987). (Box 4)
  - #315. Completed (Minimal) Mechanism for the Chemiluminescence of CH* in the Reaction of C,H, with 0(3P), p. M. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, presented at NERM XVI, June (1986); Extended Mechanism for Production of C,(d3 )by Shock Heating Acetylene Presented at 2nd International Symposium on Kinetics (July, 1989). (Box 4)
  - #316. Laser Heating for Chemical Conversions: Unique Features and Limitations, S. H. Bauer, presented at International Conference on Chemistry by IR Lasers, Leblice, Cze., September 1986. Spec. Acta 43A, 227 (1987). (Box 4)
  - #317. Conversions Over Low Barriers VIII. The Dissociation/ Association Relaxation Rate in Gaseous Formic Acid, D. B. Borchardt, J. F. Caballero and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 109, 6651 (1987). (Box 4)
  - #318. Resolution of Spectra of Mixtures, Applied to Gaseous Formic Acid, T. Wachs, D. Borchardt and S. H. Bauer, Spectrochim. Acta 43A, 965 (1987). (Box 5)
  - #319. Near Resonant V-V Energy Transfers Between CO,(00°1) and SiF, and SF, at Temperatures Below 300 K, S. Ruschin and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 91, 1699 (1987). (Box 5)
  - #320. The GasPhase Spectrum of BH,: the v, Band, K. Kawaguchi, J.E. Butler, C. Yamada, S.H. Bauer, T. Minowa, H. Kanamori and E. Hirota, J. Chem. Phys. 87, 2438 (1987). (Box 5)
  - #321. Calibration of EXAFS Radial Distributions by Debye-Scherrer Diffraction Data (I), NS. Chiu and S.H. Bauer, J. Phys~. em. 92, 65 (1988). (Box 5)
  - #322. Precision Recording of "Near-Edge" Profiles of X-ray Absorption Edges, NS. Chiu and S. H. Bauer, Anal. Chem., 60, 1562 (1988). (Box 5)
  - #323. Conversions Over Low Barriers IX, vibrational Bottlenecks at Statistical Equilibrium, S. H. Bauer, D. B. Borchardt and NS. Chiu, Ber. Bun enGesellschaft 92, 407 (1988) (Box 5)
  - #323a. Review of - Stereochemical Applications of Gas-Phase Electron Diffraction; Ed. Hargittai (Box 5)
  - #324. XANES and EXAFS Spectra of PtSnAlumina Catalysts, YX. Li, NS. Chiu, WH. Lee, S. H. Bauer and B. H. Davis. ACS Symposium Series #411; Chapter 30, p. 328, Eds. S. A. Bradley, M. J. Gattuso and R. J. Bertolacini (1989). (Box 5)
  - #325. Structure of Bimetallic Catalysts (Pt/Sn) on SiO2 and Al2O3 Supports. NEXAFS and EXAFS Diagnostics, NS. Chiu, WH. Lee, YX. Li, S. H. Bauer and B. H. Davis. Advances in HVdrotreating Catalysts, Ed. M. L. Occelli and R. G. Anthony, Elsevier, Amsterdam (1989), p. 147. (Box 5)
  - #327. Comments on Current Aspects of Chemical Kinetics A Feature Article in: Int. J. Chem. Kin. 22, 113 (1990): S. H. Bauer. (Box 5)
  - #328. Time Resolved Spectra in the Infrared Absorption and Emission from ShockHeated Hydrocarbons, S. H. Bauer and D. B. Borchardt Presented at 17th International Symposium on Shock Waves and Shock Tubes, July (1989); published in Proceedings, p. 600, API, NY (1990), Ed. Y. W. Kim. (Box 5)
  - #329. Science Literacy vs BlackBoxes; (with reference to the design of student laboratory experiments), S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Ed. 67, 692 (1990). (Box 5)
  - #330. Estimation of Homogeneous Nucleation Flux via a Kinetic Model, C. F. Wilcox, Jr. and S. H. Bauer Invited contribution to June 1990 Symposium on Nucleation, June 1820, 1990. J. Chem. Phys. 94, 8302 (1991) 11% onanc (Box 5)
  - #331. Chemiluminescent Reactions of Boron Hydrides with 0(,P) at Low Pressures, HZ. Cheng, P.M. Jeffers and S.H. Bauer: Presented at BORON (USA) II Workshop, June 7 10, 1990. Revised and expanded for Combustion Institute Chemical Physics Processes Combust io C/I9(1991). (Box 5)
  - #332. 0(3P) Attack on Boron Hydrides: II. B S H,,, HZ.Cheng and S.H.Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 94, 7076 (1991). (Box 5)
  - #333. On Relative Probabilities of Uppumping vs Pooling of Energy During Molecular Encounters, S.H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 95, 6745 (1991). 334. The Capture and Conversion of Methane Proposal for a Practical Upgrading Process, S.H. Bauer, S. Javanovic, HZ. Cheng and CL. Yu 33y.,__,Patent issued: # 5,214,226 (1993); Energy and Fuels 11, 1204 (1997) Presented at NERM 97 (June, 1997). (Box 5)
  - #334. The Upgrading of Methane Under Homogenous Thermal Conditions: An Environmental & Economic Imperative, S. H. Bauer and S. Javanovic, Energy & Fuels 11, 1204 (1997). (Box 5)
  - #334a. Application for U.S. Letters Patent, S. H. Bauer and H. Cheng, (1992) (Box 5)
  - #335. What's in a Name Transition State or Critical Transition f Structure, S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox,jr. J. Chem. Education 72, 13 (1995) (Box 5)
  - #336a. 1 Condensation Flux Estimates via a Kinetic Molecular Model, 75 S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, Jr. J. Phys. Chem. 97, 271 (1993). 1 79 (Box 5)
  - #337. 0(3P) Attack on Boron Hydrides, III: S.H. Bauer and HZ. Cheng The International J. Chem. Kinetics 26, 283 (1994) (Box 5)
  - #338. A Piston-actuated Shock Tube, with Laser-schlieren Diagnostics, Scott M. Hurst and S.H. Bauer, Rev. Sci. Inst. 64, 1342 (1993) (Box 5)
  - #339. Infrared Emissions from Shock Heated Hydrocarbons, K.M. Stephens and S.H. Bauer, Spectrochimica Acta 50A, 741756, 1994. (Box 5)
  - #340. The KineticMolecularModel for Estimating Condensation Fluxes in Supersaturated Binary Systems, S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, Jr. J. Chem. Phys. 99., 4651 (1993) (Box 5)
  - #341. KMM Interpretation of Condensation Flux Data Nonpolar vs. Highly Polar Species, S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, Jr. J. Phys. Chem. 97, 11551 (1993). (Box 5)
  - #342. Collisional Stabilization Efficiencies that Control Condesation Flux Rates in Supersaturated Vapors of nAlcohols and Water. S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, Jr. J. Phys. Chem. 98, 8721 (1994). (Box 5)
  - #343. Interpretation of Condensation Flux Rates of Supersaturated Vapors of Metallic Species, S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, Jr. Chem. Phys. Lett. 232 253 (1995). (Box 5)
  - #343a. Structures, Binding Energies, and Charge Distributions for Two to Six Atom TI, CR, FE and NI Clusters and their Relationship to Nucleation and Cluster Catalysis. A. B. Anderson, S. H. Bauer, and T. N. Rhodin (Box 5)
  - #344. The Dissociation of Dimeric Aliphatic Acids; Energetics & Kinetics C.F. Wilcox, Jr. and S.H. Bauer: J. Chem. Phys. 107, 5794 (1997) Presented at NERM 97 (June, 1997). (Box 5)
  - #345. Spectroscopic Signatures of Critical Transition Structures Scott M. Hurst, C.F. Wilcox, Jr. and S.H. Bauer J. Chem. Phys. 103, 5904 (1995) (Box 5)
  - #346. FTIR Spectra of H3CCH2Br and D3CCH2Br, C.F. Wilcox Jr. and S.H. Bauer, Spectrochimica Acta A. 52, 207 (1996) (Box 5)
  - #347. Application of the Shocktube/Laserschlieren Technique for Discriminating Between Alternate Oxidation Mechanisms, B.K. Carpenter and S.H. Bauer, Presented at the 20th Intnational Symp. on Shock Waves (Caltech), 1.995 (Box 5)
  - #348. The Gas Phase Oxidations of B, BH, BH2 and BnHm: A Review of the Thermochemistry and Kinetics, S. H. Bauer, Chem. Rev. 96, 1907 (1996) (Box 5)
  - #350. The Pyrolysis of Octafluorocyclobutane Revisited S.H. Bauer and S. Javanovic, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 30, 171 (1998) (Box 5)
  - #352. On Malonaldehyde and Acetyl Acetone: Are Theory and Experiment Compatible ? S.H. Bauer and C.F. Wilcox, 9 g7 Chemical Physics Letters, 279, 122 (1997). (Box 5)
  - #353. The Pyrolysis of Azetidine: A ShockTube Kinetics Investigation. YX. Zhang, CL. Yu and S.H. Bauer, Int.J.Chem. Kin.30, 185 (1998. (Box 5)
  - #354. The Thermochemistry of the 8oranes: CL. Yu and S.H. Bauer J Phys. and Chem. Ref. Data, 27, 807833 (1998) Pz;11_CA ,I;, S~V~_ (Box 5)
  - #355. The Thermochemical Parameters for TNAZ. Calculation of Equilibrium Product Distributions. CL. Yu, YX. Zhang and S.H. Bauer J. Mol. Struc. (THEOCHEM) 432, 63 (1998) (Box 5)
  - #356. General Potential Energy Surfaces for Catalytic Processes S.H. Bauer, J. Chem. Ed. 76, 440 (1999) (Box 5)
  - #357. Stability Tests of TNAZ Thermal and Shock Impact S.H. Bauer and YiXue Zhang, J. Energetic Materials 1,7 161 (1999) (Box 5)
  - #358. The Gas Phase Pyrolysis of TNAZ: ShockTube Kinetics YiXue Zhang and S.H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. A 102 5846 (1998) (Box 5)
  - #359. A Kinetic Mechanism for Condensation from Supersaturated Vapors That Incorporate High Levels of Dimers S.H. Bauer, YX. Zhang and C.F. Wilcox, J. Chem. Phys. ~ 110, 7926 (1999) (Box 5)
  - #360. Decomposition Mechanisms of Gaseous CN02, CONO and NN02 Energetic Materials: Re evaluations YX. Zhang and S.H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 31, 655 (1999) (Box 5)
  - #361. The Gas Phase Pyrolysis of 2Nitropropane and 2Nitropropanol YX. Zhang and S.H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. A 104, 1207 (2000) (Box 5)
  - #362. The Thermochemistry of TNAZ and of Related Species; Models for Calculating Heats of Formation C.F. Wilcox, YX. Zhang and S.H. Bauer, THEOCHEM 528 95 (2000) (Box 5)
  - #363. Kinetics of Condensation of Cs from its Supersaturated Vapor; Comment on the Entropy of a Small Cluster S.H, Bauer, YX. Zhang and C.F. Wilcox, J. Chem. Phys. 111, 8265 (1999) (Box 5)
  - #364. The Gas Phase Pyrolysis of 2,2 diNitropropane: ShockTube Kinetics YX. Zhang and S.H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem, A 04., 1217 (2000) (Box 5)
  - #365. Thermochemical and Kinetic Parameters for HBonded Clusters, Derived from Condensation Flux Data Water and nPentanol S.H. Bauer, YX. Zhang and C.F. Wilcox, J. Chem. Phys. 112, 10192 (2000) (Box 5)
  - #366. Comments on the Decomposition Mechanism and Thermochemistry of Dimethyl-nitramine 170 (2C,00 Y-X. Zhang and S.H.Bauer, Intern. J. Chem. Kin. 33, 70 (2001). (Box 5)
  - #367. The Thermochernistry of TNAZ and Related Species: Heats of Formation via G3(MP2)/B3LYP C.F. Wilcox, Y-X. Zhang and S.H. Bauer, THEOCHEM 538, 67 (2001) (Box 5)
  - #368. Comments on the Kinetics and Thermodynamics of Condensation Under Homogeneous Conditions S.H. Bauer, YX. Zhang and C.F. Wilcox API Proceedings: "Nucleation and Atmospheric Aerosols, 2000" Vol. 534, p.159 15th International Conference. Ed. B.N. Hale and M. Kulmala (Box 5)
  - #369. The Gas Phase Pyrolysis of Nitrocyclobutanes: A ShockTube Investigation Supplemented with DFT Calculations of Their Thermochernical and Structural Parameters. Yi-Xue Zhang, C.F. Wilcox and S.H. Bauer Troe Festschrift --- Zeit. Physikalische Chemie 215, 1165 (2001) (Box 5)
  - #370. On the Metastable Size Distribution of Molecular Clusters in Supersaturated Vapors: S.H. Bauer, Y-X. Zhang and C.F. Wilcox J. Chem. Phys. 114, 9408 (2001) (Box 5)
  - #372. Mass Spectrometry in the Mid1930's. Were Chemists Intrigued? J. Am. Soc. Mass Spectrom, 12, 975 (2001) (Box 5)
  - #373. Historiography of a Very Fast Gas Reaction S.H. Bauer, Chem. Rev. 102, 2893 (2002). (Box 5)
  - Reprints and Reports: Condensation, H-Bonds, Light Scattering, 1940's - 2000 (Box 6)
  - Reports, Seminar Materials, and other topics (Laboratory of Plasma Studies), 1970's - 2000 (Box 7)
  - Seminar Materials and Publications, 1970's - 2000 (Box 8)
  - Publication Material, Miscellaneous Publications, Letters, Proposals, and Notes on Various Topics, 1970's - 2000 (Box 9)